<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <color name="ic_launcher_background">#0E2A18</color>
    <string name="app_name">IDEAL Setup</string>
    <string name="btn_clear">Clear</string>
    <string name="btn_pairing_help">How do I put my device in pairing mode?</string>
    <string name="btn_provision">Provision real device</string>
    <string name="btn_refresh_wifi">Refresh</string>
    <string name="btn_simulate">Simulate</string>
    <string name="hint_device_ap">Device AP SSID (pairing)</string>
    <string name="hint_home_pass">Home Wi-Fi password</string>
    <string name="hint_home_ssid">Home Wi-Fi SSID</string>
    <string name="hint_module_id">Module ID</string>
    <string name="module_id_help">This is the identifier written to the device with AT+WRMID.\n\n• IDEAL_AP — the value the official IDEAL app always sends. It is hardcoded in the original app (it never sends anything else). Choose this to match the stock app exactly.\n\n• IDEAL_AP30_PRO / AP40 / AP60 / AP80 / AP140_PRO — these are model identifiers taken from the official app\'s internal device list (the na.c enum). The stock app does NOT write these via AT+WRMID; they are offered here only as alternatives in case a device or the cloud expects a model-specific id.\n\nIf in doubt, pick IDEAL_AP.</string>
    <string name="module_id_help_title">About Module ID</string>
    <string name="module_id_label">Module ID  ⓘ</string>
    <string name="module_id_tooltip">IDEAL_AP is what the official app sends. The model names are extra options from the app\'s device list.</string>
    <string name="pairing_help_purifier">IDEAL Air Purifier (AP30 / AP40 / AP60 / AP80 / AP140 Pro)\n\n1. Make sure the purifier is plugged in and powered on.\n2. Press and hold the device\'s Wi-Fi / power button until the LED ring flashes PINK (magenta).\n3. Pink flashing = pairing mode. The purifier is now broadcasting its own open Wi-Fi access point named \"IDEAL…\".\n4. Keep your phone next to the device, then tap \"Provision real device\". Accept the system prompt to join the IDEAL network.\n\nOfficial-app wording: \"Follow the instruction until the light of the air purifier flashes pink, then press next.\"</string>
    <string name="pairing_help_sensor">IDEAL Air Sensor (AS10 / AS15)\n\n1. Power on the sensor.\n2. Touch and hold your hand on the top of the device until the light turns WHITE.\n3. White light = pairing mode. The sensor is now broadcasting its open access point named \"ideal-add-device…\".\n4. Keep your phone close, then tap \"Provision real device\".\n\nOfficial-app wording: \"Touch and hold your hand on top of the device until the light turns white, then press next.\"\n\n(The official sensor screen shows no video — text instructions only.)</string>
    <string name="pairing_help_title">Put the device in pairing mode</string>
    <string name="show_password">Show</string>
    <string name="type_purifier">Purifier</string>
    <string name="type_sensor">Sensor</string>
    <style name="Theme.IdealSetup" parent="Theme.AppCompat.DayNight.NoActionBar">
        <item name="colorPrimary">#1B7A3D</item>
        <item name="colorAccent">#33FF66</item>
    </style>
</resources>